https://flowersbymatthew.com/about/your-privacy/

About us
Since 1986, Flowers by Matthew offers beautiful flower delivery in Long Island, designed and arranged just for you. Flowers by Matthew is the premier flower shop for all your Long Island flower delivery services. Our flower shop is located in the heart of Long Island, and we are the best florist in Wantagh, with the freshest flower delivery in New York. We also have a wide range of selection of plants and gift baskets for all occasions. Send flowers in Wantagh, Bellmore, Bethpage, East Meadown, Seaford, Massapequa...and nationwide. We make sending flowers fun!
Rewards
FAQ
Create Store Account to Join
Already have an account?
Login to check your balance or redeem rewards
×
Home
About
Your Privacy
Your Privacy
Your Privacy is Important to Us
Privacy PolicyThis privacy statement has been created in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting customer privacy.
Information We CollectIf you open an account on our site or make a purchase, we need your contact information including your name, e-mail address and mailing address to complete your transaction.
When you visit our website, we also collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. We use this information to determine our users demographics and interests, so that we can better understand and serve our users.
"Cookies"Cookies are small files which store certain information about your activity on the website and are stored on your computers hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer, so that you don’t have to reenter information you gave us on your prior visits. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but most allow you to instruct your browser to prevent the use of cookies. However, if you disable cookies, you will not be able to use certain features of this website.
Our Use and Disclosure of Your InformationWhen opening an account or making a purchase, you have an opportunity to opt-in or opt-out from receiving emails from us. If you opt-in to receive information from us, we may use your purchase history, contact information and other registration information to provide you with more relevant information and email content. We may send emails to our users regarding changes in our services or other information we believe will be of interest to our users. If you prefer not to receive these emails, you can send us an email with the subject line no emails or reply to our email with the subject line no emails.
If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities on our site, we may collect such information. We may use that information and other information that we obtain from your use of our site to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreement for Terms of Use.
We may share aggregate statistics about our sales, traffic patterns and related site information with other businesses, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.
We may share your information with reputable vendors for the purpose of sending out special offers via email and/ or in connection with the services provided by our site such as the delivery of flowers. Your information will not be shared for any other purpose and will be kept secured.
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. For example, we may be required to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that may be illegal or may expose us to legal liability.
SecurityThis site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
All user credit card information is securely communicated using secure socket layer (SSL) software, which is the industry standard and among the best software available for secure eCommerce transactions.
All user information stored on our server is stored in an encrypted format. Notwithstanding these efforts, we caution you that perfect security does not exist on the Internet.
Linked SitesIf this site contains any links to other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Changes to Privacy Statement; ConsentWe may update this Privacy Statement from time to time. We recommend checking this page periodically for changes. By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by us as described in this Privacy Statement.
Questions and CommentsWe welcome your questions and comments about this Privacy Statement.
